Kenny Becerra Programmer/ IT Analyst





About me

I am a programmer with a passion for front-end development. My background is in computer engineering and my technical career has centered around developing/managing tools for process improvement and automation using Javascript. Checkout my github to see some of the Front-end dev projects I've worked on.



Skills

HTML/CSS		
✓ HTML5 ✓ Flexbox JAVASCRIPT	✓ CSS3 ✓ CSS Grid	✓ SASS/LESS✓ Bootstrap
✓ ES5/ES6 TOOLS	✓ JQuery	✓ React / Redux
✓ NPM ✓ VS Code	✓ Webpack ✓ Git	✓ Gulp



Work Experience

Programmer/ IT Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA January 2017 - Present

Developed all User Interfaces for Third-Party Security (TSR) team vendor database using latest technologies for HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Utilized Node.js libraries to automate team process and created tools to enhance email awareness campaigns, metrics tracking and reporting.

Developed Single Page Applications (SPAs) in Sharepoint using Semantic UI, jQuery, D3.js and chart.js for TSR team to access/modify backend database via Sharepoint REST Calls.

Perform ad-hoc frontend development requests for Cybersecurity crossteam collaboration and data access to TSR team backend.

Programmer/IT Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA August 2015 - December 2016

Developed scripting solutions for Energy Procurement Support team ad-hoc requests.

Developed UI functionality for Energy Procurement System tools using SQL, and VBA.

Automated administrative tasks and workflows using VBA, python and SharePoint Rest API

Software Engineering intern at General Electric

Waukesha, WI May 2014 - August 2014

Developed scripts in Lua and Python language for software testing and data manipulation Researched integration of DDS (Data Distribution Services) for CT Scanner middleware Evaluated integration methods of DDS and updated code information/manual



Education

Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering

Florida State University



Contact

kennybecerra.j@gmail.com

https://github.com/kennybecerra

www.linkedin.com/in/kennybecerra/

